<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="noncompetitiveHeads">
		<item>Innovation Plaza -Undergraduate research in Colleges</item>

		<item>International Plaza- Foreign Students Showcase their Countries</item>

		<item>University-Industry Interface</item>

		<item>Sports Plaza</item>

		<item>EOC Corner</item>

		<item>Govt. of India Institutions</item>

		<item>Skill Development Pavilion (NSDC, New Delhi)</item>

		<item>DU Heritage Walks and Archive Tour</item>

		<item>Delhi University Women’s Association Stall</item>

		<item>Teachers Training and Academic Orientation</item>

		<item>Computerized Shooting Range-DUSC</item>

	</string-array>
    <string-array name="noncompetitive">
        <item>The Innovation Plaza is a special attraction at Antardhvani that showcases Innovation Projects, a highly successful venture of the University of Delhi. It is a unique scheme of promoting undergraduate research in colleges and inculcating innovative thinking in students. With a strong interdisciplinary flavour and structured to encourage hands-on research in college teachers and students, the projects are conducted by teams of at least three teachers and ten students from at least two departments and a Mentor from outside the institution. The highlight of the projects is the interdisciplinary nature of projects with real world exposure and societal impact. 240 projects from 62 colleges in almost every subject area and in a variety of themes will showcase the outcomes/findings at the Innovation Plaza this year. 
\n\n
Enquires may be addressed to the Innovation Desk.
			\n\n
Coordinator:
			\n
			Dr. Deepika Bhaskar, (biodeepika@gmail.com), innovationsdu@gmail.com, biodeepika@gmail.com
			\n
			Phone 011 27666227
\n\n
Exhibition based on Innovation Project on Fingerprinting
			\n\n
“The Forgotten Indian Pioneers of Fingerprint Science.” It shall highlight the key role played by two Indian Police Officers, Azizl Haque and Hem Chandra Bose in inventing the system of fingerprint classification. Although the system is still being followed in several countries across the globe, these officers never got due recognition for their scientific achievement. It shall also depict that fingerprinting has always been a part of Indian culture and civilization. This endeavour is supported by the Indian National Science Academy, New Delhi.
\n\n
Coordinators:
			\n\n
			Dr. G.S. Sodhi, sodhigs1@rediffmail.com
			\n
			Dr. Jasjeet Kaur, kjasjeet@hotmail.com</item>
        <item>In the present global environment academic and cultural ties between University of Delhi and international students from   68 countries will be showcased through an exhibition of art objects, traditional dresses, quiz and performances. Students belonging to Bhutan, Nepal, Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Japan, Korea, Iran, Iraq, Syria, Qatar, Mauritius, Jordon, Tibet and many more will host multiple programmes to interact with visitors and participants. The relationship between international students and the teaching community will be highlighted through country specific stalls. The plaza offers knowledge about places and people, games, music, dance and food.
More than 1600 international students from about 68 different countries are currently enrolled in courses at the University of Delhi.
\n\n
Coordinators: Dr Amrit Kaur Basra, Deputy Dean, Foreign Students Registry, (fsr_yahoo.com)
Dr Girish Munjal, (girishmunjal2012@gmail.com)</item>
        <item>No details available.</item>
        <item>With a focus on integrating sports achievements within the study curriculum of undergraduate students, the Sports Council will have a special programme with components such as Yoga demonstration, artistic gymnastics, display of trophies, awards and honours won by Delhi University, adventure sports with mountaineering as a focus etc. Friendly competition is encouraged through a Kabaddi match, tug- of- war and an electronic shooting range. Antardhvani will conclude with a grand parade of international and national position holders along with Inter University winners’ team. There will be a band in attendance.
\n\n
Advisor: Prof. CS Dubey (csdubey@gmail.com).
			\n\n
Coordinators: Dr. Anil Kumar Kalkal (anilkalkal@gmail.com) </item>
        <item>Delhi University strives to ensure an inclusive and equitable environment for all in order to help realize the optimum potential of students and staff in various spheres of life. The Equal Opportunity Cell of the University focuses on empowering students from the marginalized segments of society: particularly, students with disabilities. Various activities such as conversion of materials in accessible formats, providing latest technologies to students with disabilities, study tours within India and abroad and other initiatives to ensure inclusion of students with disabilities in the total life of the University are undertaken by the EOC. We also encourage such students to showcase their abilities in activities such as solo and group song, dance, instrumental performance, poetry recitation, plays and sports. During Antardhvani 2014, the EOC launched the Inclusive Print Access Project to make college and University libraries print accessible for the visually impaired. The EOC theme for Antardhwani-2015 is “Paperless Braille in the 21st Century”.
 \n\n
Dr. Bipin Tiwary (bipinkumartiwari@rediffmail.com), Dr. Anil Aneja (osd@eoc.du.ac.in)
</item>
        <item>National Book Trust will park its mobile van at Antardhvani, and the Indira Gandhi National Centre for the Arts will be exhibiting a rare collection of paintings.
\n\n
Coordinators:Dr.AnjuGupta(anjjguptaa@rediffmail.com),Dr.NishaTyagi, (drnishatyagi@hotmail.com)
\n\n
STPI and DU: The Electropreneur Park is first-of-its-kind pilot project which is going to define a collaborative framework for the Industry, Academia and promotional Govt. bodies such as  STPI to work together. Such a collaborative framework shall provide foundational support for similar future projects. It can very well be considered a significant initial step towards making India self-reliant in ESDM sector. The Electropreneur Park shall provide participation and exposure to DU faculty and students in a world-class ESDM Incubation ecosystem involving entrepreneurs, industry veterans, mentors etc., and opportunity for DU students from relevant streams to become incubatees and get exposure to current industry trends and environment.
\n\n
Coordinator: Dr. Sanjeev Singh (sanjeev.singh2@gmail.com)
			\n\n
ONGC and TBI collaboration “Yeast Oil Project”
			\n\n
Technology Business Incubator and ONGC Energy Centre Trust  are collaborating  on a project “Process Optimization for Cultivation and Oil Production from Oleaginous yeast/s: Extraction,  Characterization and Its Potential to Produce Biodiesel” Objective of the Project is to  produce biodiesel.
			\n\n
Prof. RK Saxena, TBI, South Campus (rksmicro@yahoo.co.in)
        </item>
        <item>NSDC Skill Training at DU
\n\n
NSDC has signed an MoU with DU to impart skill training for 6 sectors such as Health care, IT,  and retail,  through programmes at colleges. The STAR programme has already trained over 900 students. Currently several programmes are being planned in at least 8 colleges.
			\n\n
The National Skill Development Corporation India, (NSDC) is a one of its kind, Public Private Partnership in India. It aims to promote skill development by catalyzing creation of large, quality, for-profit vocational institutions. Its mandate is also to enable support systems such as quality assurance, information systems and train the trainer academies either directly or through partnerships.
\n\n
Coordinators: Dr. Madhusudhan (madhumargam@gmail.com), Dr. Anju Gupta (anjjuguptaa@rediffmail.com)</item>
        <item>The Heritage Walk beckons visitors to experience the history of the University of Delhi through the Archive located on three floors of the Viceregal Lodge. While the building as a whole is an Archive, visits at specified halting points gives an opportunity to understand the past and present through written records, artefacts and visual representation.  There are rare photographs of the Uprising of 1857, a narrative of Delhi University’s inception and growth, and a moving view of Shaheed Bhagat Singh’s jail cell. The extended tour can take visitors to   sites located on the Northern Ridge where rebels and the British soldiers had fought for the retention of Shahajahanabad.  The stall will also screen documentaries on the history of Delhi University.
\n\n
Guided tours starting at Stall:\n
20 February, 2015			12:15 pm ---4:30 pm\n
21 February, 2015			10:30 am ---4:30 pm\n
22 February, 2015			10:30 am ---4:30 pm\n
\n\n
Coordinator: Dr. Amrit Kaur Basra (amritdcac@gmail.com)
			\n
Bookings: (infocentre@du.ac.in) (incharge@uic.ac.in)
        </item>
        <item>
            DUWA Souvenir Shop
			\n\n
            The official line of Delhi University souvenir items has been launched recently. The primary purpose of this activity is to promote the DU brand and to simultaneously inculcate a sense of pride and belonging amongst the students and other members of the DU community. The design and sale of the souvenir items is being managed by DUWA, which is a part of the Delhi University family.  Antardhvani mascot Haathi will be found in the souvenir stall.  There has been a great demand for the following items which shall be available at very reasonable prices: folders, bags, pens, key chains, mugs, etc.
			\n\n
            The Mind Body Centre
			\n\n
Promoting the wellness of the women students at Delhi University is the prime objective of this Centre. Problems of the mind and body are interconnected, and are dealt by the expertise of the physicians, naturopath and counsellor at the Centre. In addition to free consultation, the practice of yoga and acupressure techniques is also used at the Centre.
			\n\n
The other activities at DUWA include:
			\n
Preschool facility and Crèche for children of  University employees and others.
			\n
Free tuition facility for underprivileged children
Foreign language class.
			\n
Cancer Awareness programme.
			\n
Food stall at Antardhvani
\n\n
Advisor: President, DUWA (duwaassociation@gmail.com)
        </item>
        <item>The Centre for Professional Development in Higher Education (CPDHE)   takes the lead role in teacher training and evolving new pedagogical practice. Keeping in view the interdisciplinary character of the training in  the year 2014-15   CPDHE conducted  four week Orientation Programme ( four in number) for entry level teachers and three week Refresher courses in Sanskrit, Hindi, and Life Sciences, Environmental Studies, Mathematical Sciences and Women Studies each. It conducted a cycle in training teachers in the interactive pedagogy of the ‘flipped’ classroom with virtual/online classes at three centres, one being outside campus: Sri Venkateswara College. CPDHE conducted an International workshop for teachers and students where Prof James Avantakis from Sydney University talked on Innovative Teaching Technologies. CIC also participated in this endeavour. Workshop on use of technologies in teaching encouraged teachers to  deploy learning devices and IT programmes in the class room.
Teachers\' learning is from presentations and projects, with the teacher being involved in the
            classroom and library.  To date about 520 teachers participated in these courses.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Sports Council will create an arena for a computerized shooting range. This enjoyable activity is competitive and energetic.  It tests skill such as concentration, mental strength and marksmanship.  The shooting range keeps track of game records which can be used for handing out quick prizes for the fun of it.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>