<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="specialHeads">
        <item>Four Food Courts</item>
        <item>Gyanodaya Express- DU’s College on Wheels</item>
        <item>Community Radio Stall</item>
        <item>NCWEB- Non-collegiate Women’s Education Board</item>
        <item>Adventure Sports: An Introduction to Mountaineering</item>
        <item>Friendly Kabaddi Match: Vice Chancellor’s team vs Principals’ team</item>
        <item>NSS- National Service Scheme</item>
        <item>NCC- National Cadet Core</item>
        <item>Institute of Life Long Learning (DU-e-learning Outreach)</item>
        <item>CIC-Cluster Innovation Centre</item>
	</string-array>

	<string-array name="special">
		<item>
Food Courts at Antardhvani this year will be positioned at four locations.  One multi cuisine outlet has a large seating area. It offers a simple snack to a full meal, and will be presenting a large variety over the festival days: Indian popular food, regional meals, Italian pizza and pasta, Chinese items, sandwiches and burgers and much more.... A second court will specialize in Dilli Ka Khana, Delhi’s famed street food, a third venue will offer Indian quick foods, meals on a platter, and a fourth venue will focus on South Indian cuisine. In addition, DUWA will also set up a food stall.  Tea, coffee and beverages are available at all food courts and all items will be moderately priced.

Coordinators:  Prof. Mridula Gupta, (mridula_du@yahoo.com) 9810868230.
Prof. Rajesh, 9873302532. Prof. Suresh Rai.
			</item>
		<item>‘Gyanodaya’, the unique programme of taking about 900 students and 100 supporting staff on a train journey. Placing the itinerary in the context of Gandhi and hands-on learning, the philosophy urges young people to understand India, to appreciate its diversity, and to carry the message of good will. The project contributed immensely towards nation building by instilling these students with a pride in our North-East region as the latest journey, Gyanodaya V, had students visiting all the 8 states in the North-East and conducting micro projects. A book on the journey will be released at Antardhvani, 2015.
</item>
        <item>
DUCR has been restructured. The new location and services have created an efficient environment and easy access for student learners. The Community Radio has been broadcasting programmes relating to social issues, career counseling, livelihood and broad areas of education. Conducting courses on media and journalism, the radio offers hands-on training, which is very popular.

        </item>
        <item>
Delhi University was established in 1922 and by an amendment of Delhi University Act in 1943, Women students were enabled to take some of the examination of the University with special coaching but without attending regular classes. This gave shape to the Non­-collegiate Women’s Education Board (NCWEB), which is now well established. The Board began functioning in September, 1944 with 3 students. At present, the enrolment is more than 15,000. The classes are held at 14 centres at various colleges and regular interactive programmes bring students to the campus. This unique experiment is no longer only for women who cannot attend class but for those are seeking a flexible study schedule. </item>

		<item>
Linked to the NCC programme at DU, focus on mountaineering will bring attention to fitness and training.  A climbing wall is to be installed at Antardhvani for demonstration and instruction. Alongside, information on adventure sports will be available through pamphlets, videos and photos. Coordinated by DU students who have outstanding achievements in mountaineering, the stall will encourage interaction to understand the physical and psychological advantages of such sports.
\n\n
            Coordinator: Dr. Anil Kalkal, Sports Council (anilkalkal@gmail.com)
/n
            Student Mountaineers:
            \n
            Akash Jindal, former student (akash_jindal7@yahoo.com)
Saachi Soni (sonisaachi254@gmail.com)</item>
		<item>India is  the host to World\'s first Kabaddi League. India won the Kabaddi World Championship in 2007.  This year Kabaddi has been selected because this traditional Indian game has achieved national and international status. The revival and professionalizing conveys that local sporting activities requiring minimum equipment and facilities encourage community interaction. Extending such a mode, the University of Delhi has created a forum for a friendly match on the final day of Antardhvani.  This will be played between the Vice Chancellor’s team and the Principals’ team. The spirit of working together in day to day administration carries over into sportsmanship on the field. The cheering squads will support both the teams! </item>
		<item>NSS Centre of the University of Delhi will showcase its activities undertaken by the 62 NSS units in various colleges of the University. The major activities conducted  in this session were Women’s  Safety and Cleanliness drive in colleges. Street plays will be performed by NSS volunteers of different Units on various social issues.

Programme Coordinator: Capt. Parminder Sehgal, (nssuniversityofdelhi2012@gmail.com)</item>
		<item>Antardhvani 2015 will showcase cadets of different units and of different colleges performing the inaugural NCC parade with a spectacular guard of honour to the Chief Guest. It will march through the stadium area of the campus. Students shall also display skills in combat, first aid, disaster management, firefighting and other activities of NCC. The cadets will also perform as volunteers for security duties during Antardhvani 2015. 
NCC Incharge: Capt. Parminder Sehgal (parmindersehgal3@gmail.com) </item>
		<item>The Institute of Lifelong Learning (ILLL) is dedicated to the cause of those who believe that learning is not age-bound nor classroom-bound, but it takes place throughout life and in all kinds of situations. The Institute has been striving to develop state-of-the-art infrastructure to help Delhi University’s teaching and non-teaching staff members and students in capacity building in ICT skills. The Institute of Lifelong Learning is a nodal agency for creation and uploading of e-content for undergraduate students of the University of Delhi and has more than 500 learning units available in the form of lessons, quiz, e-labs, panel discussion and lectures, some of them bilingual. The ILLL is also engaged in e-Pathshala programme of the UGC and is working extensively with the National Mission for ICT linked education. </item>
		<item>The Cluster Innovation Centre – or CIC as it is popularly known – is the spearhead for the transformative processes in education that are underway in the University of Delhi. It is an endeavour to harness the passion and dedication of bright young minds with some of the major challenges of India and of civil society. The hallmark of the CIC is ‘out of the box’ thinking and action with ‘hands on’ applications through a transdisciplinary route.
Cluster Innovation Centre (CIC), was set up by the University of Delhi in 2011 with the objective of fostering an ecosystem of innovation and connecting research with application for the benefit of society. Its objective is to develop ideas into innovative applications to solve real world problems through application-oriented research. The focus at CIC is on developing affordable and sustainable innovations to reach a large number of people. CIC has introduced highly innovative curricula and pedagogy.
The CIC has begun to create new benchmarks in learning and knowledge creation leading to society’s benefits. It justifiably, attracts attention and admiration from several parts of India and the world.

Recently the DUCIC has set up the Technology Business Incubator (MSME) which is a start-up accelerator and entrepreneur programme founded by the MSME to foster a proactive community of entrepreneurs. It was established with MoMSME Support Grant for Technology Entrepreneurship in 2014 to encourage entrepreneurs/incubatees to try out their innovative ideas, processes or products at the laboratory or workshop stage and beyond, to carry forward the idea from its mere conception to know-how and then to the  how- to- do- it stage.
The centre focuses on fostering innovation in the form of viable business plans to solve real world problems. The main focus is on integrating innovation in finding solutions to everyday problems. TBI helps ideas turn into business solutions by providing funding, co-working space and mentoring from experts to accelerate the growth of high-potential start-ups.</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>